**TANMAY JOSHI** 

UI/UX DESIGNER

tanmayjoshi2205@gmail.com



/tanmay\_

🎉 /tanmayjoshi

/tanmayjoshi96

/tanmay\_who

/idiot.tanmay

### ABOUT ME

I am a 20 years young UI/UX designer from the oldest technical institute of Asia, Indian Institute of Technology. Roorkee. I have 2 years worth of experience in problem solving through design. Working In different groups of IITR, I have touched each design sub-group. Stories inspire me to be more creative and conclusive towards life's daily problems. Trekking to different places and exploring the core of the cities helps me in understanding different cultures and hence different perspectives.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

### GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Geek Gazette | August 2015 - Present

Geek gazette is the official tech-magazine of IIT Roorkee. Here, me along with 18 other designers design every aspect of magazine. You can check out previous issues at <a href="https://www.issuu.com/geekgazette2">www.issuu.com/geekgazette2</a>

### UI/UX DESIGNER

SDSLabs | Jan2016 - Dec2016

SDSLabs is the official tech group of IIT Roorkee.

Here, a group of 7 designers create apps to solve the everyday problems faced by the students of IITR. You can check out our portfolio at <a href="https://www.sdslabs.co">www.sdslabs.co</a>

# EDUCATION

# B.TECH (PRODUCTION & INDUSTRIAL)

IIT ROORKEE | July 2015 - Present

P&I is a combination of mechanical engineering and industrial engineering and management science. It is a branch of engineering concerned with the development, improvement, implementation and evaluation of integrated systems.

# CBSE | 12 BOARD

Delhi Public School, Jodhpur | 2002 - 2014

# INTERESTS

FOOTBALL POP MUSIC

TRAVELLING HARRY POTTER

MARVEL PHOTOGRAPHY

# ACHIEVEMENTS

AIR 3869 | JEE ADVANCED 2015
91.2% | CBSE 12TH BOARD
LAUNCHED 2 APPS IN COLLEGE
LAUNCHED TEE DESIGN START-UP

# SKILLS

